this is a really boring video and it's
really short get a Gmail account the
end that's it that's all there is to it
why should you get a Google Gmail
account do you hate Google find I don't
care you know what get it for free and
don't put anything on there you care
about right obviously don't dependent
depend on it for anything
private you don't really need that you
really don't need that but uh in another
video I'll show you how you can use
Gmail to create a lot of pseudo accounts
particularly for GitHub and other places
like that that all point to that
singular Gmail account and then what you
can do with the Gmail account is you can
forward that Gmail off to your proton
mail and that will be where you maintain
your primary email account now if you
already have a preferred email provider
I'm not telling you what to do I'm just
telling you if you don't have an email
provider and you're looking for one that
is kind of Loosey Goosey you can go
ahead and create a YouTube account and a
and a Gmail account and yes Google is
going to search all that stuff and
they're going to mine you to death but
it doesn't matter because you're just
the only reason you're using that is so
that you can sign up for different
things you can have one or two or three
or 10 you know get up accounts and they
all use the same email because of the
Plus in invol and that is a separate
video so
that's it for this video get yourself a
Gmail account if you want to follow
along in the Boost I'm going to be doing
that so make sure you do
that um